Finding Aid for the Collection of Broadside Ballads from England, Ireland, and the United States LSC.0605
UCLA Library Special Collections
- England
  - Taylor, T., ca. 1859-1899
    - Miller of the Dee. Mackay, Charles, 1814-1889, Miller of the Dee. London, England; Taylor, Printer, Brick Lane, Bethnal Green, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: T6; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 14 × 8 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - My pretty Jane. Young Napoleon: or, The bonny bunch of roses. Fitzball, Edward, 1792-1873, My pretty Jane. London, England; London: Published at Taylor's Song Mart 93, Brick Lane, Bethnal Green, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: T7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - My pretty Jane. Young Napoleon: or, The bonny bunch of roses. Young Napoleon: or, The bonny bunch of roses. London, England; London: Published at Taylor's Song Mart 93, Brick Lane, Bethnal Green, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: T7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Nigger gal. The nigger gal. London, England; Published at Taylor's Song Mart, 93, Brick Lane, Spitalfields near the Railway Arch, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: 6:2:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Railroad to hell: from dissipation to poverty, and from poverty to desperation. Railroad to hell: from dissipation to poverty, and from poverty to desperation. London, England; Taylor, Printer, 92 & 93, Brick Lane. N.E., [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: 6:11:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Rifleman Jack. Rifleman Jack. London, England; Taylor, Printer, 92, Brick Lane, Bethnal Green. N.E., [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: 6:13:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Soldier's dream. Campbell, Thomas, 1777-1844, The soldier's dream. London, England; Taylor. Printer, 92, Brick Lane, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: 8:1:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Sweet cottage maid. The sweet cottage maid. London, England; Printed and Published at Taylor's Song Mart, [93, Brick] Lane, Bethnal Green, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: 8:5:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Veteran. Bayly, Thomas Haynes, 1797-1839, Veteran. London, England; London: Published at Taylor's Song Mart, 93, Brick Lane, Bethnal Green, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: 8:11:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 17 × 8 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Village born beauty. Village born beauty. London, England; London: Printed and Published at Taylor's Song Mart, 93, Brick Lane, Bethnal Green, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: 8:11:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 22 × 8 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Warrier's return.1 Garbutt, W., Warrier's return. London, England; Published at Taylor's Song Mart, (Late Neesom), 93, Brick Lane, Spitalfields, near the Railway, [between 1859 and 1899]., Shelfmark: 8:12:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 16 × 8 cm. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Taylor, William, ca. 1831-1836
    - All the blue bonnets over the border. Highland soldier. Brown, G., Highland soldier. London, England; Printed by Taylor, 14, Waterloo-Road, Lambeth, [1836]., Shelfmark: 4.16.16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 23 × 16 cm. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - All the blue bonnets over the border. Highland soldier. Scott, Walter, Sir, 1771-1832, All the blue bonnets over the border. London, England; Printed by Taylor, 14, Waterloo-Road, Lambeth, [1836]., Shelfmark: 4.16.16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 23 × 16 cm. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Excursion to Putney. The excursion to Putney. London, England; Printed by Taylor, 14, Waterloo Road, [1836]., Shelfmark: 4.3.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 23 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Gallant troubadour. Come Chloe, and give me sweet kisses. On this cold flinty rock. Hanbury Williams, Charles, Sir, 1708-1759, Come Chloe, and give me sweet kisses. London, England; Printed by Taylor, 16, Waterloo Road, [between 1831 and 1832]., Shelfmark: 4.8.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Gallant troubadour. Come Chloe, and give me sweet kisses. On this cold flinty rock. Brandon, Isaac, On this cold flinty rock. London, England; Printed by Taylor, 16, Waterloo Road, [between 1831 and 1832]., Shelfmark: 4.8.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Gallant troubadour. Come Chloe, and give me sweet kisses. On this cold flinty rock. Scott, Walter, Sir, 1771-1832, The gallant troubadour. London, England; Printed by Taylor, 16, Waterloo Road, [between 1831 and 1832]., Shelfmark: 4.8.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Sing the sailor's welcome home. Sing the sailor's welcome home. London, England; Printed by W. Taylor, wholesale, 16, Waterloo Road, near the Coburg Theatre, [between 1831 and 1832]., Shelfmark: 6:18:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 21 × 10 cm. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - True picture of the London gin palaces. Morgan, John, A true picture of the London gin palaces. London, England; Printed by Taylor, 14, Waterloo Road, [1836]., Shelfmark: 8:9:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Thompson, T., 18--
    Printed in Dudley, England.
    - Rigs and sprees of this town. Hill, William, The rigs and sprees of this town. Dudley, England; T. Thompson, Printer, Dudley, [18--]., Shelfmark: 6:13:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 21 × 8 cm. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Tracy and Nussey, 18--
    - Dialogue between a Catholic and Protestant. A dialogue between a Catholic and Protestant. Leeds, England; Printed for Tracy and Nussey, York Street, Leeds, [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:16:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Turner, J., ca. 1797-1846
    Printed in Coventry, England.
    - Catskin: or, The wandering lady. Catskin: or, The wandering lady. Coventry, England; Turner, Printer, Coventry, [between 1797 and 1846]., Shelfmark: 3:9:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 20 × 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Death and the lady: or, The great messenger of mortality. Death and the lady: or, The great messenger of mortality. Coventry, England; Printed by J. Turner, High Street, Coventry, [between 1797 and 1846]., Shelfmark: 3:16:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 21 × 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Merry broom fields: or, The west country wager. The merry broom fields: or, The west country wager. Coventry, England; Printed by J. Turner, high Street, Coventry, [between 1797 and 1846]., Shelfmark: Turn1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Turkey factor. The Turkey factor. Coventry, England; Turner, Printer, Coven[try], [between 1797 and 1846]., Shelfmark: 8:10:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 33 × 22 cm. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Unidentified publishers (Addlehead-Christmas), ca. 1780-1880
    Printed in England.
    - Addlehead's farewell to Old England!!! Addlehead's farewell to Old England!!!., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:1:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 17 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - After the temper is over. A country life for me. A country life for me., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:1:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - After the temper is over. A country life for me. After the temper is over., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:1:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Anchor's weighed. The wild boar hunt. Arnold, Samuel James, 1774-1852, The anchor's weighed., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:1:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Anchor's weighed. The wild boar hunt. The wild boar hunt., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:1:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Babes in the wood. The babes in the wood., [England], [between 1780 and 1850]., Shelfmark: 3:3:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 21 × 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bateman's tragedy. Bateman's tragedy., [England], [between 1780 and 1850]., Shelfmark: 3:3:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 20 × 27 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Beamish v. Johnson. Beamish v. Johnson., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:4:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 21 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Beautiful Jane. I wish they'd do it now. Beautiful Jane., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:4:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Beautiful Jane. I wish they'd do it now. I wish they'd do it now., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:4:4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bells of Saint Peter. Condon, Timothy, The bells of Saint Peter., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:4:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 18 × 11 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Berkshire tragedy: or, The Wittam [i.e.Wittenham] miller, with an account of his murdering his sweetheart, &c. The Berkshire tragedy: or, The Wittam [i.e.Wittenham] miller, with an account of his murdering his sweetheart, &c.., [England], [between 1780 and 1850]., Shelfmark: 3:4:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 22 × 33 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Berkshire tragedy: or, The Wittam [i.e.Wittenham] miller. The Berkshire tragedy: or, The Wittam [i.e.Wittenham] miller., [England], 1796., Shelfmark: 3:4:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 20 × 31 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Best of any: or, The postman's knock. Johny the Poacher, The best of any: or, The postman's knock., [England], [1876?]., Shelfmark: 3:4:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 38 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Billy make room for your father. Billy make room for your father., [England]; Printed for the vendors., [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:5:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bold Irishman. Though I am now a very little lad. Though I am now a very little lad., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 3:6:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bold Irishman. Though I am now a very little lad. The bold Irishman., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 3:6:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bold trooper. Spring, Spring. I have heard sweet music stealing. Eccles, J. H., I have heard sweet music stealing., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 3:7:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bold trooper. Spring, Spring. I have heard sweet music stealing. Planche…, J. R. (James Robinson), 1796-1880, Spring, Spring., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 3:7:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bold trooper. Spring, Spring. I have heard sweet music stealing. The bold trooper., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 3:7:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bonnie soldier laddie. John Bull and the Yankey [i.e. Yankee]. Send back my Barney to me. Send back my Barney to me., [England], [ca. 1861]., Shelfmark: 3:7:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bonnie soldier laddie. John Bull and the Yankey [i.e. Yankee]. Send back my Barney to me. John Bull and the Yankey [i.e. Yankee]., [England], [ca. 1861]., Shelfmark: 3:7:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bonnie soldier laddie. John Bull and the Yankey [i.e. Yankee]. Send back my Barney to me. Bonnie soldier laddie., [England], [ca. 1861]., Shelfmark: 3:7:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Brave "24th". True as the stars that are shining. True as the stars that are shining., [England], [not before 1879]., Shelfmark: 3:7:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Brave "24th". True as the stars that are shining. The brave "24th"., [England], [not before 1879]., Shelfmark: 3:7:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Brave collier lad. Dawning of the day. Brave collier lad., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:7:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Brave collier lad. Dawning of the day. Dawning of the day., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:7:9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Chairing Day: a new song / by William Steggall. Steggall, William, The Chairing Day: a new song., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:9:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 22 × 10 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Chairing song, June 30th, 1790. Chairing song, June 30th, 1790., [England], 1790., Shelfmark: 3:9:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 32 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Christmas carols. Christmas carols., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 3:10:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified publishers (Copy-Full), ca. 1780-1880
    - Copy of verses on the Afghan War. Copy of verses on the Afghan War., [England], [between 1878 and 1880]., Shelfmark: 3:12:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Copy of verses written on the present state of old England: what will become of England? Copy of verses written on the present state of old England: what will become of England?., [England], [1879?]., Shelfmark: 3:12:20; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Country lad am I. A country lad am I., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:13:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Crafty lover: or, The lawyer-out-witted. The crafty lover: or, The lawyer-out-witted., [England], [between 1780 and 1850]., Shelfmark: 3:13:20; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 21 × 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Dame of honor: or, Hospitality. D'Urfey, Thomas, 1653-1723, The dame of honor: or, Hospitality., [England], [between 1780 and 1850]., Shelfmark: 3:15:6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 20 × 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Dandy petticoat. The dandy petticoat., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:15:8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 9 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Dear friends of old. Will a monkey climb a tree. Dear friends of old., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:15:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Dear friends of old. Will a monkey climb a tree. Will a monkey climb a tree., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:15:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Don't try it on. Union Jack of old England. Union Jack of old England., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3.17.8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Don't try it on. Union Jack of old England. Don't try it on., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3.17.8; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Down among the coals. When the cock begins to crow. Down among the coals., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3.17.9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Down among the coals. When the cock begins to crow. Linn, Harry, When the cock begins to crow., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3.17.9; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Down by the old mill stream. The red plaid shawl. The red plaid shawl., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 3.17.12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Down by the old mill stream. The red plaid shawl. Down by the old mill stream., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 3.17.12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Drinan dhun. The drinan dhun., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 3.18.5; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 17 × 8 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Effects of love. Do it again. Do it again., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.1.1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Effects of love. Do it again. Effects of love., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.1.1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Excellent new song call'd The trusty and true English-man An excellent new song call'd The trusty and true English-man., [England], [1711]., Shelfmark: 8:10:1; 1 sheet ([2] p.); 30 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Fair Rosamond: Henry the second's concubine. Deloney, Thomas, 1543?-1600, Fair Rosamond: Henry the Second's concubine., [England], [between 1780 and 1850]., Shelfmark: 4.4.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 19 × 31 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Far, far upo[n] the sea. Mackay, Charles, 1814-1889, Far, far upo[n] the sea., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.4.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 29 × 10 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Fate of Dr. G------y! The fate of Dr. G------y!., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.5.3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Foggy dew. The foggy dew., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.6.12; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 16 × 8 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Footprints in the snow. Our sailors on the sea. Our sailors on the sea., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.6.14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Footprints in the snow. Our sailors on the sea. Footprints in the snow., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.6.14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Freemasons' song. A man that is married. Freemasons' song., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.7.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Freemasons' song. A man that is married. A man that is married., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.7.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Full account of the founding of her Majesty's ship "Eurydice" and 300 British sailors. A copy of verses on the foundering of the ship. A copy of verses on the foundering of the ship., [England], [1878]., Shelfmark: 4.7.14; 1 folded sheet ([4] p.): 4 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Full account of the founding of her Majesty's ship "Eurydice" and 300 British sailors. A copy of verses on the foundering of the ship. Full account of the founding of her Majesty's ship "Eurydice" and 300 British sailors., [England], [1878]., Shelfmark: 4.7.14; 1 folded sheet ([4] p.): 4 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified publishers (Gallant-In), 18--
    - Gallant female sailor. The gallant female sailor., [England], [not before 1845]., Shelfmark: 4.8.3; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 23 × 10 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Gaping goose. The gaping goose., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.8.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Gerard's introduction. Gerard's introduction., England; Printed at the Election Squib Mart, Grand-Parade., [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.9.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 23 × 11 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Give me the man of honest heart. My bonny Yorkshire lass. Give me the man of honest heart., [England], [1876?]., Shelfmark: 4.9.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Give me the man of honest heart. My bonny Yorkshire lass. My bonny Yorkshire lass., [England], [1876?]., Shelfmark: 4.9.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Glorious women of old England: a new song in praise of the women of old England! The glorious women of old England: a new song in praise of the women of old England!., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.10.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Grand conversation on Napoleon. The brave old oak. The grand conversation on Napoleon., [England], [not before 1821]., Shelfmark: 4.12.14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Grand conversation on Napoleon. The brave old oak. Chorley, Henry Fothergill, 1808-1872, The brave old oak., [England], [not before 1821]., Shelfmark: 4.12.14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Grandmother's chair. There goes Flaherty. There goes Flaherty., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.13.3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Grandmother's chair. There goes Flaherty. Read, John, 1839-1920, My grandmother's chair., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.13.3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Gravedigger. Two shilling suit. Two shilling suit. London, England; H. […] Printer […] London, [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.13.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Gravedigger. Two shilling suit. The gravedigger. London, England; H. […] Printer […] London, [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.13.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Hampstead is the place to ruralise. Evangeline. Evangeline., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.14.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Hampstead is the place to ruralise. Evangeline. Williams, Watkin, Hampstead is the place to ruralise., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.14.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Have another try. Have another try., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.14.19; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Have you seen the Shah? Have you seen the Shah?., England, [1873]., Shelfmark: 4.15.2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Heaven protect our soldiers and sailors who have gone to the Russian war. Heaven protect our soldiers and sailors who have gone to the Russian war., [England], [not before 1874]., Shelfmark: 4.15.9; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Home rule for Paddy's land. Working overtime. Home Rule for Paddy's land. Newcastle, England, [1886]., Shelfmark: 4.16.18; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 27 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Home rule for Paddy's land. Working overtime. Working overtime. Newcastle, England, [1886]., Shelfmark: 4.16.18; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 27 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - I am so very shy. The village maiden. The village maiden., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 4.18.3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - I am so very shy. The village maiden. I am so very shy., [England], [1875?]., Shelfmark: 4.18.3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - I can't bear a cur at my heels. There never was a coward where the shamrock grows. Molloy, James L., 1837-1909, There never was a coward where the shamrock grows., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.18.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - I can't bear a cur at my heels. There never was a coward where the shamrock grows. I can't bear a cur at my heels., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.18.4; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - I must go out on Sundays! Banks, G. Linnaeus (George Linnaeus), 1821-1881, I must go out on Sundays!., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.18.14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - I tickled her under the chin / sung by Ralph Mason. Baker, Harry, I tickled her under the chin., [England]; [M]usic at Alfred Hays, 4, Royal Exchange-buildings, & 82, Cornhill, [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.18.15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - I will stray to yon glen. The tailor. I will stray to yon glen., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.18.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 32 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - I will stray to yon glen. The tailor. The tailor., [England], [18--]., Shelfmark: 4.18.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 32 × 20 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - In loving memory of H. R. H. Princess Alice, (of Great Britain), who died Saturday December 14, 1878: aged 35 years In loving memory of H. R. H. Princess Alice, (of Great Britain), who died Saturday December 14, 1878: aged 35 years., [England], [1878]., Shelfmark: 4.19.13; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 8, Folder 15)